whatdropsnow.com 2018-10-15

# Privacy Policy | What Drops Now

_This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 24, 2018._

We take your privacy very seriously and are committed to being transparent with how we use your information. This website ([www.whatdropsnow.com](http://www.whatdropsnow.com/)), mobile application and any of our services and sites directing you to this Privacy Policy are controlled by Titel Media GmbH, Ritterstraße 9, 10969 Berlin, Germany (collectively "we" or "us"). 

**Data controller/responsible body** :

Titel Media GmbH, Ritterstraße 9, 10969 Berlin, Germany

Duly represented by David Fischer, Jürgen Hopfgartner

 **Data process manager** : Michiel Slot, [dpo@highsnobiety.com](mailto:dpo@highsnobiety.com)

 **Summary**

 **Purpose of data collection, data processing and data use:**

Titel Media is engaged in operating online publications covering forthcoming trends and news in fashion, art, music, and culture. Titel Media collects and processes personal data for the following purposes:

Operation of the website, including statistical analysis of the use

Provision of content

Advertising

Execution of contracts

 **Groups of people concerned and the associated data and category of data:**

Customer and user data, data from partner companies that are needed to fulfill the purpose.

 **Children under 16**

Our website is not directed toward children under 16 and we will not knowingly collect information for any child under the age of 16. 

If you are the parent of a child under the age of 16 and have a concern regarding your child’s information on our website, please contact us at [info@highsnobiety.com](mailto:info@highsnobiety.com).

 **Recipients or groups of recipients to whom data may be disclosed:**

Public authorities in connection with an overriding legal regulation, contractors in connection with a partnership in accordance with Article 28 of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), external partners and internal departments of Titel Media GmbH to fulfill the purpose. 

**Time limits for the deletion of data:**

Under statutory provisions, a variety of obligations and periods apply with regard to the keeping of data. Once these retention periods have expired, the corresponding data must be erased as a matter of routine. Any data not affected by this is deleted if the purposes mentioned above cease to apply. 

**Transfer of data to third countries:**

By using social plugins, such as facebook like button, data may be transferred to a third country.

 **Legal basis for the collection and processing of personal data:**

Legal basis for the processing of personal data on the basis of the user’s consent is Art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR.

Legal basis for the processing of personal data which is necessary for the conclusion or performance of a contract entered in the interest of the user is Art. 6 (1) lit. b GDPR. This also applies to pre-contractual processes.

Legal basis for the processing of personal data which is required to fulfil a legal obligation concerning Titel Media is Art. 6 (1) lit. c GDPR.

Legal basis for the processing of personal data which is necessary in order to realize a legitimate interest held by either Titel Media or a third party, except where such considerations are overridden by the need to protect the user’s interests or fundamental rights, is Article 6 (1) lit. f GDPR.

 **Our Privacy Policy Explains:**

What information we collect and why we collect it (section I. - VI.)

How we use that information (section I. - VI.)

Your rights with regard to the processing of personal data by Titel Media (section VII.)

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or would like to know more about what information we collect and store, please contact us at: [info@highsnobiety.com](mailto:info@highsnobiety.com)

 **Information We Collect:**

We collect information to provide better services to our users and improve our business. We collect information in two ways:

 **Information you give us or information provided through a social network**. For example, some of our services require you to sign up for an account, provide information for a contest or award, or link an account through a social network. The information we collect may include email, name, phone number, address, or credit card information. Such information is necessary to render the services requested and/or to provide contractual services. Legal basis for such data processing is Article 6 (1) lit. a, b or f GDPR. Unless statutory provisions provide otherwise, the data will be deleted if the purpose cease to apply, e.g. if the services are performed in full or if you unsubscribe from our services.

When you contact us, either by e-mail or by using our contact form, we collect the data you have submitted with your request (e.g. name. e-mail) and may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. Legal basis for such data processing is Article 6 (1) lit. b and lit. f GDPR. Unless statutory provisions provide otherwise, the data will be deleted if the purpose cease to apply, e.g. if we have processed your request.

We work with social networks including, but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, Google Plus, Snapchat, Instagram, and YouTube. We have access to information you directly provide and information through those social networking services based on your privacy settings on those networks. Please see section IV. below for further details. Such information serves to enhance the usability of our services. Legal basis for such data processing is Article 6 (1) lit. f GDPR. Unless statutory provisions provide otherwise, the data will be deleted if the purpose cease to apply.

 **Information we get from your use of our services**. We may collect usage information when you visit different parts of our site or use our applications. We may also automatically collect certain technical information such as device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, device type, unique device identifiers, and mobile information if you use a mobile device to access the site). Please see section I. below for details. Such information is necessary to provide our services and is used in anonymized or pseudonymized form only. Legal basis for such data processing is Article 6 (1) lit. f GDPR. Unless statutory provisions provide otherwise, the data will be deleted if the purpose cease to apply.

 **Affiliate Links**

Our website contains affiliate links to websites of our partners. When following the link, the website you visit may use cookies. The use of cookies is the sole responsibility of the respective website operator. 

**Information we share**

We do not share personal information with companies, outside organizations and individuals unless one of the following circumstances apply:

 **With your consent**. We will share personal information with companies, outside organizations or individuals if we have your consent to do so. We may also seek your additional consent for purposes subsequently notified to you.

 **For external processing**. We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. If personal data is transferred to or processed in countries outside the European Union, we make sure that our contractors guarantee an adequate level of data protection. 

**For legal reasons**. In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We will share personal information with companies, outside organizations or individuals if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of our users or the public as required or permitted by law.  

 **In case of a sale or asset transfer**. If we become involved in a merger, acquisition or other transaction involving the sale of some or all of our assets, user information, including personal information collected from you through your use of our services, could be included in the transferred assets. Should such an event occur, we will use reasonable means to notify you and ask for your consent where applicable.

 **In anonymous form for business purposes**. We may share anonymous, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners such as businesses which we have a relationship with, advertisers or connected sites. For example, we may share information to show trends about the general use of our services.

 **Information Security**

We work hard to protect our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold however no website is entirely secure. You should protect the account information in your possession as well. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at [info@highsnobiety.com](mailto:info@highsnobiety.com).

## I. Cookies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by us and our advertising and marketing partners, affiliates, or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We use cookies to remember users' settings (e.g. geographic location) and for authentication. You can decide whether to accept cookies. 

When visiting our website, we will ask you for your consent to use certain cookies. You may at any time revoke your consent to such use by using the opt-out button or the opt-out functions described below or by sending an e-mail to [info@highsnobiety.com](mailto:info@highsnobiety.com). 

In addition, users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level by changing your browser settings (mostly found under “Options” or “Settings” in the browser menu). You have the choice of accepting all cookies, being informed about each cookie or refusing all. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html> cookies.

If you choose not to accept cookies on our website, it is possible that the functionality of our website may be limited and some services may not be usable.

We and our service providers, marketing partners, and affiliates may use advertising cookies to deliver ads that we believe are more relevant to you and your interests. For example, we may use targeting or advertising cookies to customize the advertising and content you receive on our site, to limit the number of times you see the same ad on our site and to help measure the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns. These cookies remember what you have looked at on the site and other sites, and may be combined with other information acquired from third parties. 

You may visit the links below to opt-out of cookies from over 50+ major third party behavioral advertising providers:

\- Network Advertising Initiative: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/

\- European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance: http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/

\- http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices

\- Digital Advertising Alliance: http://www.aboutads.info/choices/

Please see below for a full list of cookies and detailed information on the associated processing of personal data and how to opt-out of the use:

### I. 1. Cookies we use with your consent only

 **Google Analytics.** We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA

(“Google”), on our website. Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies”, text files that are saved on your computer and that enable your use of the website to be analyzed. The cookie-generated information about your use of our website is usually transmitted to and stored on a Google server in the United States. However, if you are in a country that is a member state of the European Union or a contracting party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area, and if IP address anonymization has been activated on our website, Google will first truncate your IP address. Only by way of exception will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the United States and truncated there. Google will use this information on our behalf for the purposes of analyzing how you use our website, compiling reports on website activity and providing further services related to website and internet use to the website operator. The IP address transmitted through Google Analytics from your browser will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You can disable cookies by setting your browser accordingly; however, if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of our website. You can also prevent the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of this website (including your IP address) being transmitted to and processed by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available here: [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de)

As an alternative to installing the browser plug-in, particularly in internet browsers on mobile devices, you can prevent the collection of data by Google Analytics by clicking this link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>

This will save an “opt-out” cookie to your device, meaning that none of your data will be collected on this website by Google Analytics.

More detailed information about the function of Google Analytics and the terms of use and privacy policy relevant to this service can be found under [http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html) and [http://www.google.de/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy/). We would also like to point out that our website uses Google Analytics with the anonymizeIP extension so that IP addresses are only processed further in an abbreviated form to prevent them being directly linked to a particular individual.

 **Google AdSense.** Our website also utilizes Google AdSense, a Google Inc. service that allows Google to place automatically generated, content-related advertisements on our website. For further information on Google AdSense, please see [http://www.google.co.uk/adsense](http://www.google.de/adsense). Similarly to Google Analytics, Google AdSense uses cookies that are saved on your computer and that enable analysis of your use of our website. Additionally, Google AdSense utilizes “web beacons” (invisible graphics), which also enable an evaluation of your use of our website. The information regarding the use of this website (including your IP address) generated by cookies and web beacons, and the delivery of advertising formats, are transferred to a Google server, where they are saved. Google uses such information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on the website activities and to provide other services to us in relation to website and internet use. Furthermore, Google may pass on this data to its advertising partners. We would like to point out that, in contrast to Google Analytics, Google has as yet not taken measures to anonymize your IP address for its Google AdSense service. Therefore, in addition to the previously mentioned data relating to your use of our website, your IP address will also be transferred to, and saved on, a Google server. You can disable cookies by setting your browser accordingly.

 **Google DoubleClick Ad Exchange** and **Google Tag Manager**. Our website uses Google Double Click Ad Exchange and Google Tag Manager software provided by Google. These services allow website providers to address their visitors in a targeted fashion by displaying personalized, interest-based advertisements when they visit other websites that are part of the Google Display Network. Google utilizes cookies to analyze how users use a website. The information collected with these cookies form the basis for interest-based advertising. To do so, Google stores a small sequence of numbers in the browser of the visitor calling on the website. This number is used to record the visits to the website and collect anonymized data on how the website is being used. No personal data are collected in the process. If you subsequently visit another website that is part of the Google Display Network, you will be served advertisements that are very likely to be related to the products or information that you have previously viewed. You can permanently deactivate the cookies used by Google if you click on the following link and download and install the plug-in contained therein: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin>. Alternatively, you can deactivate the use of cookies through third parties by visiting the deactivation page of the Network Advertising Initiative at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> and following the opt-out instructions contained therein. Further information on Google remarketing and the privacy policy of Google can be found at: <http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/>.

 **Google DoubleClick for Publisher**. Our website uses DoubleClick for Publishers ("DFP"), a service of Google. DFP is a platform for the placement, management and optimization of ads on websites. DFP allows us to present personalized ads to website visitors who have shown interest in certain content areas. This is made possible through an analysis of their use of our website, including other site pages, and on other websites within the Google display network (Google itself, Google Ads, and other websites). For this purpose, Google uses cookies, which are stored on your computer. DoubleClick cookies do not contain or store any personal data of users. You can deactivate personalized Google ads in your browser by clicking the "Turn off" button under "Ads Personalization Across the Web" at <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>, or, if you use the Google Chrome, Firefox or Internet Explorer browser, by installing the DoubleClick opt out extension offered for your browser at <http://www.google.de/settings/ads>.

 **Quantcast**. Our website uses Quantcast Measurement, a service provided by Quantcast Corp., 201 3rd Street, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA („Quantcast“). Quantcast provides us with a service for audience measurement and for advertising purposes. Using Quantcast allows us to address the users of our website in a targeted manner. Quantcast collects information on how you use our services, including your IP address (not your name, e-mail address or other personally identifiable information). Such information is stored on Quantcast’s servers in the US and is provided to us in aggregated form only. Further information on the processing and use of data by Quantcast can be found in Quantcast’s privacy policy: <https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/>

You may opt-out of data collection by Quantcast at any time by following this link: <https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/>

**Scorecard Research**. Our website uses Scorecard Research, a service provided by Full Circle Studies, Inc., 11950 Democracy Drive, Reston, VA 20190, USA („Scorecard“). Scorecard collects information on how you use our services, including information about your operating system, browser type and website preferences and your activities on our website. Such information is used to create reports on the use of our website that helps us to understand our user’s behaviour and to provide with you content and advertising based on your interests and preferences. Further information on the processing and use of data by Scorecard can be found in Scorecard‘s privacy policy: [www.scorecardresearch.com/privacy.aspx](http://www.scorecardresearch.com/privacy.aspx)

You may opt-out of data collection by Scorecard at any time by following this link: 

 **comScore**. Our website uses audience measurement services provided by comScore Inc. („comScore“). comScore uses cookies to collect information about our audience (e.g. demographic data such as region, language, age group, gender), their behavior (e.g. devices they use, how they use our content or websites they visit) and the efficiency of our advertising campaigns. In most cases, this information is pseudonymized or anonymized. Further information on the processing and use of data by comScore can be found in comScore‘s privacy policy: <https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy> and here: <https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/GDPR/General-Data-Protection-Regulation-GDPR?cs_edgescape_cc=DE>

**Nielsen DCR.** Our website uses Nielsen Digital Content Rankings („DCR“), a digital content and advertising meaurement service provided by The Nielsen Company (US) LLC, 85 Broad Street, New York, NY 10004, USA („Nielsen“). Nielsen DCR uses cookies to collect information about the content that was viewed (e.g. which ad campaign), where the content was viewed and general information about the device on which the content was viewed (e.g. tablet or smartphone, advertising identifier, IP address, operating system). Nielsen does not identify the users. Such information may be enhanced with other data sources (e.g. social media, excluding individually identifying details) and is used to create insights, reports and analyses about the composition of the audience that viewed certain content, or about the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. Further information on the processing and use of data by Nielsen can be found in Nielsen’s privacy policy: <http://www.nielsen.com/us/en/privacy-statement/digital-measurement.html#how-we-collect-data>.

You may opt-out of data collection by Nielsen at any time by following this link: <http://www.nielsen.com/content/corporate/policy/en/cookie-policy.html>.

We will only use such cookies with your prior consent. Legal basis for such data processing is Article 6 (1) lit. a GDPR. Unless statutory provisions provide otherwise, the data will be deleted if you revoke your consent or if the purpose cease to apply. In any cases, personal data will be deleted after 24 months at the latest.

### I. 2. Other cookies we use

 **Facebook Custom Audiences**. Our website uses the “Custom Audiences” remarketing service provided by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook"). This service allows us to advertise products and services to the visitors of our website in a targeted fashion by displaying personalized, interest-based Facebook ads to the website’s visitors, when they use the Facebook social network. This tag establishes a direct connection to the Facebook servers when you visit our website. It allows the Facebook server to record which of our webpages you have visited. Facebook allocates this information to your personal Facebook user account. Additional information regarding the collection and utilization of your data by Facebook, your rights in relation to these data and the possibilities to protect your privacy can be found in the privacy policy of Facebook at <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>.

If you do not want Facebook to assign this information directly to your Facebook user account, you can deactivate the “Custom Audiences” remarketing service by using the following link: <https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads>. You must be logged in at Facebook to do so.

 **Chartbeat**. Our website uses Chartbeat, a service provided by Chartbeat, Inc., 826 Broadway, 6th Floor, New York, NY 10003, USA („Chartbeat“). Chartbeat is an internet technology company that provides real-time website analytics to monitor content performance. It collects anonymous user data to provide information about how our website is being used and gives us an indication of the content that is of most interest to our website visitors. This includes what pages users are clicking on, how long users spend on each page, whether users are commenting on a page, and whether users are scrolling down pages they click on. This information allows us to provide content that is more useful and relevant for the users of our websites. For details of Chartbeat’s privacy policy, please visit [http://www.chartbeat.com](http://www.chartbeat.com/). 

**New Relic APM**. Our website uses New Relic Application Performance Monitoring, a service provided by New Relic Inc., 101 Second Street, 15th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94105 („New Relic“). New Relic APM allows us to monitor and analyse the technical performance of our services and to detect possible faults. New Relic APM collects application data, such as information on the user’s browser and browser add-ons or the hard- and software used. Further information on the processing and use of data by New Relic can be found in New Relic's privacy policy under: <https://newrelic.com/privacy>.

 **Visual Website Optimiser** : Our website uses Visual Website Optimiser, a service provided by Wingify Software Pvt. Ltd., 14th Floor KLJ Tower, Netaji Subhash Place, Pitam Pura, Delhi 110034, India („Visual Website Optimiser“). Visual Website Optimiser uses cookies to identify a user’s browser and to analyse the use of our website in order to increase the user friendliness of our services. Visual Website Optimiser collects data in anonymized form only. Further information on the processing and use of data by Visual Website Optimiser can be found in VWO‘s privacy policy: https://vwo.com/privacy-policy/

You may opt-out of data collection by Visual Website Optimiser at any time by following this link: <https://vwo.com/opt-out/>

Our services are mainly financed by advertising revenues. The use of cookies helps to improve the quality of our website and services and serves to finance our services and is used in anonymized or pseudonymized form only. Legal basis for such data processing is Article 6 (1) lit. f) GDPR. Unless statutory provisions provide otherwise, the data will be deleted if the purpose cease to apply. In any cases, personal data will be deleted after 24 months at the latest.

## II. Account

We offer users the opportunity of creating want-lists of products or trademarks and liking and following them. In order to use these functions, you must create a user account. Within the framework of the registration and use of this service, we will collect and process the following personal data: name, email address, currency and products/brands you follow, add to your want-list or like or would like. Based on your preferences, we show you a personalized stream of products on our website.

Legal basis for such data processing is Article 6 (1) lit. b and f GDPR. Unless statutory provisions provide otherwise, the data will be deleted if the purpose cease to apply, e.g. if you delete your account. 

## III. Links to external social networks and social media widgets

Our website includes links to social networks and social media features. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies providing them. Please note that Titel Media is not liable for the privacy policies of these companies. We recommend you to read the privacy policies of those companies after you get to one of their websites.

 **Facebook**. **** Our website has links to our Facebook page and uses social plugins provided by the social network facebook.com. The sole responsibility for Facebook and its website lies with Facebook Inc.

The plugins are identifiable by a Facebook logo (white letter f on blue background or a thumb up icon) or the notice “Facebook Social Plugin”. For a full list of all social Plugins please see <https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins?locale=en_US>.

When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plugin of Facebook, your browser establishes a direct connection to Facebook servers. Facebook directly transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling Facebook to receive information about your having accessed the respective page of our website. Thus we have no influence on the data gathered by the plugin and inform you according to our state of knowledge:

The embedded plugins provide Facebook with the information that you have accessed the corresponding page of our website. If you are logged into Facebook, your visit can be assigned to your Facebook account. If you interact with the plugins, for example by clicking “Like”, or entering a comment, the corresponding information is transmitted from your browser directly to Facebook and stored by it. Even if you are not logged into Facebook, there is possibility that the plugins transmits your IP-address to Facebook.

For the information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by Facebook, as well as your rights in this respect and settings options for protecting your privacy please visit Facebook's privacy policy: 

<https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>

.

If you are a Facebook member and do not want Facebook to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your member data already stored by Facebook, please log off Facebook before entering our website. Further you can block Facebook social Plugins by using add-ons for your browser, like the “Facebook Blocker“ under 

<http://webgraph.com/>

**Login with Facebook**. Our website also allows you to register or sign-up to our services using your Facebook account. If you connect to whatdropsnow.com through Facebook, we collect and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any information you agreed that Facebook could provide to us through its API. Such information may include your name, profile picture, e-mail address, gender, birthday, location and other information you make publicly available via Facebook. 

Such information serves to enhance the usability of our services. Legal basis for such data processing is Article 6 (1) lit. f GDPR. Unless statutory provisions provide otherwise, the data will be deleted if the purpose cease to apply.

For further information regarding the purpose and scope of data collection, and regarding the further processing and use of your data by Facebook, see Facebook’s own privacy rules. These are available online at [www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://de-de.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php). There you will find, amongst other things, information regarding settings for the protection of your privacy and regarding your further rights regarding the collecting, processing and use of your data by Facebook.

 **Google+ and Twitter**

Our website also has links to our Google+ and Twitter pages and uses social plugins provided by the social network of Google+ and Twitter. Sole responsibility for Google+ and its websites lies with Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA; for Twitter with Twitter Inc., 1355 Market St., Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103. 

Using the Google +1 button you can publish information globally. Using the Google +1 button you and other users will receive personalised content from Google and its partners. Google stores the information that you have +1’d content as well as information regarding the page that you were on when you +1’d. Your +1s may be shown together with your profile name and your photo in Google services such as search results, your Google profile or other web sites or advertisements in the Internet. Google records information on your 1+ activities in order to improve Google services for you and others. A global public Google profile, which must at least contain the name selected for this profile, is required to use the Google +1 button. This name will be used for Google services. In some cases this name may even replace a different name that you have used to share content via your Google account. Your Google profile’s identity may be shown to users knowing your email address or have other personally identifiable information about you.

In addition to the purposes described above the information you provided will be used in accordance with Google’s privacy policy. Google may publish consolidated statistics about +1 users’ activities or share them with users and partners such as publishers, advertisers or associated web sites.

When you use Twitter and the “Re-Tweet” feature the pages you visited will be linked to your Twitter-account and published to other users. This also involves transferring data to Twitter. Please note that we as providers of the pages have no knowledge as to the contents of the submitted data or its use by Twitter. 

For further information regarding the purpose and scope of data collection, and regarding the further processing and use of your data by Google+ and Twitter, see the privacy rules of Google+ and Twitter. These are available online at [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy](http://www.google.com/intl/de/policies/privacy) for Google+ and at [https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en ](https://twitter.com/privacy) for Twitter. There you will find, amongst other things, information regarding settings for the protection of your privacy and regarding your further rights regarding the collecting, processing and use of your data by Google+ and Twitter.

 **Instagram**

Our website has links to our Instagram page and uses social plugins provided by the social network of instagram.com. The sole responsibility for Instagram and its website lies with Instagram LLC, 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA (“Instagram”).

When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plugin of Instagram, your browser establishes a direct connection to the Instagram servers. Instagram directly transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling Instagram to receive information about your having accessed the respective page of our website. Thus we have no influence on the data gathered by the plugin and inform you according to our state of knowledge:

The embedded plugins provide Instagram with the information that you have accessed the corresponding page of our website. If you are logged into Instagram, your visit can be assigned to your Instagram account. If you interact with the plugins, the corresponding information is transmitted from your browser directly to Instagram and stored by it. Even if you are not logged into Instagram, there is possibility that the plugins transmits your IP-address to Instagram.

If you are an Instagram member and do not want Instagram to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your member data already stored by Instagram, please log off Instagram before entering our website.

For further information regarding the purpose and scope of data collection, and regarding the further processing and use of your data by Instagram, see Instagram’s own privacy rules. These are available online at <https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388>. There you will find, amongst other things, information regarding settings for the protection of your privacy and regarding your further rights regarding the collecting, processing and use of your data by Instagram.

 **Snapchat**

Our website has links to our Snapchat page and uses social plugins provided by the social network of Snapchat. The sole responsibility for Snapchat and its website lies with Snapchat, Inc., Attn: copyright Agent, 63 Market Street, Venice, CA 90291, USA (“Snapchat”). 

When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plugin of Snapchat, your browser establishes a direct connection to the Snapchat servers. Snapchat directly transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling Snapchat to receive information about your having accessed the respective page of our website. Thus we have no influence on the data gathered by the plugin and inform you according to our state of knowledge:

The embedded plugins provide Snapchat with the information that you have accessed the corresponding page of our website. If you are logged into Snapchat, your visit can be assigned to your Snapchat account. If you interact with the plugins, the corresponding information is transmitted from your browser directly to Snapchat and stored by it. Even if you are not logged into Snapchat, there is possibility that the plugins transmits your IP-address to Snapchat.

If you are a Snapchat member and do not want Snapchat to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your member data already stored by Snapchat, please log off Snapchat before entering our website.

For further information regarding the purpose and scope of data collection, and regarding the further processing and use of your data by Snapchat, see Snapchat’s own privacy rules. These are available online at <https://www.snap.com/en-US/privacy/privacy-policy/>. There you will find, amongst other things, information regarding settings for the protection of your privacy and regarding your further rights regarding the collecting, processing and use of your data by Snapchat.

 **YouTube**

Our website has links to our YouTube page and uses social plugins provided by the social network of YouTube. The sole responsibility for YouTube and its website lies with YouTube LLC with its main office at 901 Cherry Avenue, San Bruno, CA 94066, USA. YouTube is represented by Google Inc. with its main office at 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. 

When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plugin of YouTube, your browser establishes a direct connection to the YouTube servers. YouTube directly transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling YouTube to receive information about your having accessed the respective page of our website. Thus we have no influence on the data gathered by the plugin and inform you according to our state of knowledge:

The embedded plugins provide YouTube with the information that you have accessed the corresponding page of our website. If you are logged into YouTube, your visit can be assigned to your YouTube account. If you interact with the plugins, the corresponding information is transmitted from your browser directly to YouTube and stored by it. Even if you are not logged into YouTube, there is possibility that the plugins transmits your IP-address to YouTube.

If you are a YouTube member and do not want YouTube to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your member data already stored by YouTube, please log off YouTube before entering our website.

For further information regarding the purpose and scope of data collection, and regarding the further processing and use of your data by YouTube, see YouTube’s own privacy rules. These are available online at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. There you will find, amongst other things, information regarding settings for the protection of your privacy and regarding your further rights regarding the collecting, processing and use of your data by YouTube.

 **Spotify**

Our website includes functions of the Spotify music service, provided by Spotify AB, Birger Jarlsgatan 61, 113 56 Stockholm, Sweden (“Spotifiy”). When you visit a page of our website that contains a Spotify plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to the Spotify servers, enabling Spotify to receive information that you have visited our website. If you click the Spotify button while being logged in to your Spotify account, you can link the content of our pages to your Spotify profile. Thus, Spotify can associate visits to our pages with your user account.

More information on the purpose and scope of data collection, and regarding the further processing and use of your data by Spotify can be found in the Spotify privacy policy at <https://www.spotify.com/de/legal/privacy-policy/>.

If you do not want Spotify to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your member data already stored by Spotify, please log off Spotify before entering our website.

## IV. Newsletter

You have the opportunity to receive a newsletter containing targeted information via our web service. In this case we must collect and save your email address, which we will only use to send the newsletter. You can unsubscribe via our website at any time. At the end of the newsletter you will find a link intended for this purpose and provides a simple way to cancel the newsletter. In this case your data will be deleted. 

If you have expressly consented to receiving our newsletter, the legal basis for such processing of personal data is Art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR. In case we are entitled to send a newsletter based on your previous purchase of goods or services, legal basis for such processing of personal data is § 7 (3) of the German Act Against Unfair Competition (UWG). Unless statutory provisions provide otherwise, the data will be deleted if the purpose cease to apply, e.g. if you unsubscribe from the newsletter.

## V. Local Storage - HTML5

We may use Local Storage, such as HTML5 to store user preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity may also use HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. Legal basis for such data processing is Article 6 (1) lit. f GDPR. Unless statutory provisions provide otherwise, the data will be deleted if the purpose cease to apply.

## VI. Log information

When you use our services or view content provided by us, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This information may include:

Details of how you used our service, such as your navigation paths and search queries.

Mobile related information if you access our website using your mobile device.

Internet protocol address.

Device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.

Cookies that may uniquely identify your browser, mobile device, or your account.

Browser type, operating system, and other technical information.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve marketing, analytics, and the products and services we offer you. Such information is used in anonymized or pseudonymized form only. Legal basis for such data processing is Article 6 (1) lit. f GDPR. Unless statutory provisions provide otherwise, the data will be deleted if the purpose cease to apply.

 **You may at all times object to the use of personal data for the abovementioned purposes by informal notification by written letter to Titel Media GmbH, Ritterstraße 9, 10969 Berlin, Germany, or by e-mail to**[info@highsnobiety.com](mailto:info@highsnobiety.com) **.**

## VII. Your right to information and other rights of the persons affected

 **Right to information**

You have the right to obtain confirmation as to whether or not your personal data is being processed by us. Where that is the case, you have the right to access to the personal data and the following information:

the purposes of the processing;

the categories of personal data concerned;

the recipients or categories of recipient to whom the personal data have been or will be disclosed, in particular recipients in third countries or international organisations;

where possible, the envisaged period for which the personal data will be stored, or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine that period;

the existence of the right to request from the controller rectification or erasure of personal data or restriction of processing of personal data concerning the data subject or to object to such processing;

the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority;

where the personal data are not collected from the data subject, any available information as to their source;

the existence of automated decision-making, including profiling, referred to in Article 22(1) and (4) GDPR and, at least in those cases, meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and the envisaged consequences of such processing for the data subject.

Where personal data is transferred to a third country, you have the right to be informed of the appropriate safeguards pursuant to Article 46 GDPR relating to the transfer.

 **Right to rectification**

You have the right to obtain the rectification of inaccurate or incomplete personal data. 

**Right to erasure**

You have the right to obtain the erasure of personal data where one of the following grounds applies:

the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed;

you withdraw the consent on which the processing is based according to of Article 6 (1) lit a or Article 9 (2) lit. a GDPR, if there is no other legal ground for the processing;

you object to the processing pursuant to Article 21 (1) GDPR and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing, or you object to the processing pursuant to Article 21 (2) GDPR;

the personal data have been unlawfully processed;

the personal data have to be erased for compliance with a legal obligation in Union or Member State law to which Titel Media is subject;

the personal data have been collected in relation to the offer of information society services referred to in Article 8 (1) GDPR.

If Titel Media has made personal data public and is obliged to erase the personal data, Titel Media, taking account of available technology and the cost of implementation, takes reasonable steps, including technical measures, to inform controllers which are processing the personal data you have requested the erasure by such controllers of any links to, or copy or replication of, those personal data.

The right to erasure shall not apply to the extent that processing is necessary:

for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information;

for compliance with a legal obligation which requires processing by Union or Member State law to which Titel Media is subject or for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller;

for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

 **Right to restriction of processing**

You have the right to obtain restriction of processing where one of the following applies:

you have contested the accuracy of the personal data, for a period enabling Titel Media to verify the accuracy of the personal data;

the processing is unlawful and you oppose the erasure of the personal data and request the restriction of their use instead;

Titel Media no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of the processing, but is required by you for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims;

you have objected to processing pursuant to [Article 21](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-21-gdpr/) (1) GDPR pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of Titel Media override yours

Where processing has been restricted under the above, such personal data shall, with the exception of storage, is only processed with your consent or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims or for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person or for reasons of important public interest of the Union or of a Member State.

I you have obtained restriction of processing you will be informed before the restriction of processing is lifted.

 **Notification regarding rectification or erasure of personal data or restriction of processing**

Titel Media will communicate any rectification or erasure of personal data or restriction of processing carried out in accordance with the above to each recipient to whom the personal data have been disclosed, unless this proves impossible or involves disproportionate effort. On your request, Titel Media informs you about those recipients.

 **Right to data portability**

You have the right to receive the personal data you have provided to Titel Media in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to another controller, where:

the processing is based on consent pursuant to Article 6 (1) lit. a of Article 9 (2) or on a contract pursuant to Article 6 (1) lit. b GDPR; and

the processing is carried out by automated means.

In exercising your right to data portability, you have the right to have the personal data transmitted directly from one Titel Media to another controller, where technically feasible.

The right to data portability shall not apply to processing necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest.

 **Right to object**

You have the right to object, on grounds relating to your particular situation, at any time to processing of personal data concerning you which is based on point Article 6 (1) lit. a or lit. f GDPR, including profiling based on those provisions. Titel Media no longer processes the personal data unless Titel Media demonstrates compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

Where personal data are processed for direct marketing purposes, you have the right to object at any time to processing of personal data concerning you for such marketing, which includes profiling to the extent that it is related to such direct marketing.

If you object to processing for direct marketing purposes, the personal data is no longer being processed for such purposes.

 **Automated individual decision-making, including profiling**

You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning him or her or similarly significantly affects him or her.

This shall not apply if the decision:

is necessary for entering into, or performance of, a contract between the data subject and a data controller;

is authorised by Union or Member State law to which the controller is subject and which also lays down suitable measures to safeguard the data subject’s rights and freedoms and legitimate interests; or

is based on the data subject’s explicit consent.

In all such cases, please refer to us by written letter to Titel Media GmbH, Ritterstraße 9, 10969 Berlin, Germany, or by e-mail to [info@highsnobiety.com](mailto:info@highsnobiety.com).

 **Right to revocation**

You may at all times revoke consent to the processing of personal data by using our **revocation form**.

 **Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority**

Without prejudice to any other administrative or judicial remedy, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your habitual residence, place of work or place of the alleged infringement if you consider that the processing of personal data by Titel Media relating to you infringes the provisions oft he GDPR.

If you have any questions about data protection, please feel free to contact us at any time using the details given above.

## VIII. Changes 

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.
